Geopolitical fracturing and the race for
AI domination have shattered the global
economic order. As Indian enterprises
navigate this period of existential
risks, the India risk management awards
is back for its 12th edition. This year
marks a milestone as ICICI Lombard
celebrates 25 years. We will recognize
excellence in risk management and lend
strategic perspectives on India's charge
in the AI space. If you are building
resilience in the face of ground
shifting risks, then nominate yourself
today large, mid and small companies.
ICICI Lumbard and CNBC TV18 present
India Risk Management Awards season 12
nominations open.